artpromotivate.com 2019-07-21

# Privacy Policy and Disclosure | Artpromotivate

**Privacy Policy and Disclosure  for www.ArtProMotivate.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at artpromotivate@gmail.com.

At ArtProMotivate.com , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by  ArtProMotivate.com  and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites,  ArtProMotivate.com  makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
ArtProMotivate.com does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on  ArtProMotivate.com .  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to  ArtProMotivate.com  and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense  
Shareasale.com  
Commission Junction: www.cj.com  
artlicensinginfo.com  
DrawPJ.com  
unconventionalguides.com  
LinkConnector.com  
Wix.com  
Ejunkie.com  
Problogger.com  
NorthLightShop.com

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ArtProMotivate.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

ArtProMotivate.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  ArtProMotivate.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**FTC Disclosure** :

Some of the links you see at this art blog link to affiliate programs for which Graham Matthews is a member. Graham Matthews receives a small percentage of sales from purchases after visiting these websites. This aids in supporting costs in running a website such as this, and helps me to continue promoting talented artists for free. Be assured - I only recommend resources which I truly believe in and are helpful for all artists!   
  
If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact me.  
  
These are the affiliate programs at this website:  
(many are at the resources page)

Shareasale.com

Commission Junction: www.cj.com  
artlicensinginfo.com  
DrawPJ.com  
unconventionalguides.com  
LinkConnector.com   
Wix.com  
Ejunkie.com  
Problogger.com  
NorthLightShop.com  
Artbizcoach.com  
Webydo.com  
Ecwid.com
